<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Smith</title>
    <link>https://crsmithdev.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chris Smith</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 21:00:11 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://crsmithdev.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Logistic Regression</title>
      <link>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/ml-logistic-regression/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 21:00:11 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/ml-logistic-regression/</guid>
      <description>This is the second in a series of posts in which I explore concepts in Andrew Ng&amp;rsquo;s Introduction to Machine Learning course on Coursera. In each, I&amp;rsquo;m implementing a machine learning algorithm in Python: first using standard Python data science and numerical libraries, and then with TensorFlow.
Logistic regression is similar to linear regression, but instead of predicting a continuous output, classifies training examples by a set of categories or labels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linear Regression</title>
      <link>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/ml-linear-regression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 21:00:11 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/ml-linear-regression/</guid>
      <description>This is the first of a series of posts in which I&amp;rsquo;ll be exploring concepts taught in Andrew Ng&amp;rsquo;s Introduction to Machine Learning course on Coursera. As a CS student, I enjoyed doing odd or extra things with my assignments — I found it added a greater challenge and allowed me to learn outside the scope of the class in a well-structured way. So, as I progress through this course, I&amp;rsquo;ll be posting another take on the coursework in Python, using a Jupyter notebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hotel Gracery Shinjuku</title>
      <link>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/hotel-gracery-shinjuku/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 21:00:11 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/hotel-gracery-shinjuku/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://crsmithdev.com/images/hotel-gracery.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;alt&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Hotel Gracery is located in &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kabukich%C5%8D,_Tokyo&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Kabukichō, Tokyo&lt;/a&gt;, just northeast of Shinjuku station. It looks something like an Alienware &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.alienware.com/landings/desktops.aspx&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;tower&lt;/a&gt;, especially when viewed from the street as pictured above. Notably, the cinema attached to the hotel features a &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.rocketnews24.com/2014/12/11/full-size-godzilla-head-to-terrorize-moviegoers-and-hotel-guests-in-tokyo-starting-next-spring/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;full-size Godzilla head&lt;/a&gt; which can be seen peeking over the rooftop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yushima Tenman-gū</title>
      <link>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/yushima-tenman-gu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2016 21:00:11 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/yushima-tenman-gu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://crsmithdev.com/images/yushima-shrine.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;alt&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yushima_Tenman-g%C5%AB&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Yushima Tenman-gū&lt;/a&gt; is a small Shinto shrine in northern Tokyo I found after getting off at the wrong train station on the way to &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ueno_Park&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Ueno Park&lt;/a&gt;.  The building pictured above is actually not the main shrine itself, but one of the other buildings in the complex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mode Gakuen Cocoon Tower</title>
      <link>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/mode-gakuen-cocoon-tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2016 11:47:20 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/mode-gakuen-cocoon-tower/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://crsmithdev.com/images/mode-gakuen.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;alt&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my favorite buildings in Tokyo is the &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mode_Gakuen_Cocoon_Tower&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Mode Gakuen Cocoon Tower&lt;/a&gt;.  Located in Shinjuku, it&amp;rsquo;s one of the most striking buildings on the skyline.  The above is shot from an unusual angle, looking up from an opening in the pedestrian tunnel that leads west from the station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Cumulus</title>
      <link>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/book-review-cumulus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2016 17:02:42 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/book-review-cumulus/</guid>
      <description>Cumulus is a new novel from Eliot Peper, set in an near-future Bay Area remade by severe economic inequality, ubiquitous surveillance and consolidation of corporate power. While it works better as a commentary than as a novel, the dystopia it presents is a plausible evolution of current economic and social trends and worth a read by fans of the genre, or anyone interested in where another decade or so might take us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://crsmithdev.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 12:01:44 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsmithdev.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Chris Smith. I live in San Francisco, California and do software, startup and mindfulness things.
Most recently, I was an engineering manager at Uber. I joined the company in 2014 as an engineer, and was a manager and individual contributor in the data engineering and developer experience organizations. My data engineering team of 15 people was responsible for Uber&amp;rsquo;s primary realtime business intelligence pipeline, and scaled backend systems and data products through several years of Uber&amp;rsquo;s aggressive business and employee growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running Redis 2.6 on Docker</title>
      <link>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/running-redis-26-on-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2013 11:34:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/running-redis-26-on-docker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;docker&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the end of my free tier eligibility looming on AWS, I took advantage of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://developer.rackspace.com/devtrial/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Rackspace developer discount&lt;/a&gt; and set up a new account and personal server this weekend.  One of the technologies I&amp;rsquo;ve been most interested in recently is &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.docker.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt;, a container engine for Linux which aims to be the intermodal shipping container for applications and their dependencies.  A brand-new box seemed like the perfect time to dig in to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Blog Refresh with Bootstrap and Static</title>
      <link>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/a-blog-refresh-with-bootstrap-and-static/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2013 11:34:28 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/a-blog-refresh-with-bootstrap-and-static/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, I finally set up a blog on my domain, having owned but left it unused for over a year.  My needs were simple:  it was to be a completely static site, hostable on GitHub Pages or Dropbox, and the focus of the project was in &lt;strong&gt;no&lt;/strong&gt; way to be the technology or process of creating and maintaining it.  Despite the part of me that automatically geeked out at the opportunity to build my own completely custom blog generator from scratch, the point of doing it was to provide myself with a straightforward platform for &lt;em&gt;writing&lt;/em&gt;, not to go on a technical adventure in creating one.  Although I&amp;rsquo;ve only written two posts on it so far, the effort was successful: in short order, I&amp;rsquo;d set up &lt;a href=&#34;http://octopress.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Octopress&lt;/a&gt; and had it deploying to Pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Better Email Habits with Mailbox</title>
      <link>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/building-better-email-habits-with-mailbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 11:31:53 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsmithdev.com/blog/building-better-email-habits-with-mailbox/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As my first-ever blog post, I&amp;rsquo;m presenting my recent experience with the recent email app, &lt;a href=&#34;http://mailboxapp.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Mailbox&lt;/a&gt;.  This is less about the app itself, however (or it recently being snapped up by Dropbox for $100 million), but more about how I used it to help me examine and improve my behavior when it comes to handling and communicating via email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://crsmithdev.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsmithdev.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Arrow Arrow is a simple, lightweight Python library, inspired by moment.js and requests, that provides a sensible, intelligent way of creating, manipulating, formatting and converting dates, times and timestamps. Arrow is a drop-in replacement for Python date objects.
 Fully implemented, drop-in replacement for datetime Supports Python 2.6, 2.7, 3.3, 3.4 and 3.5 Time zone-aware &amp;amp; UTC by default Provides super-simple creation options for many common input scenarios Updated .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>